Contact

jonest7108@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tjonesbsn84 (LinkedIn) evaunt.me/4v1uVK/TamikaJones (Other)

Top Skills

Nursing Critical Care Acute Care

Certifications

NIHSS

Family Nurse Practitioner

PCCN

Registered Nurse

Honors-Awards

10+ years in healthcare

Atlanta Journal Constitution Nominee 2017

March of Dimes Nurse of The Year Finalist

Daisy Award Three Time Nominee

Tamika Jones, MSN, FNP-BC, PCCN, CCRN

Travel Nurse at Freedom Healthcare Staffing Greater Atlanta Area

Summary

Board Certified FNP also working as an ICU RN. With over 8 years of nursing experience in Oncology, Cardiopulmonary, Burns and Critical Care, I have had quality experiences which have developed my nursing skills and encouraged me to pursue a higher level of nursing. My ultimate goal, Doctorate of Nursing.

Experience

WellStar Health System
Critical Care Registered Nurse
June 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month)
Marietta, Georgia

Medical ICU RN - Relief Charge, ECMO Specialist, CRRT

Freedom Healthcare Staffing Travel Nurse April 2020 - April 2020 (1 month)

Comprehensive Spine and Pain of Villa Rica Family Nurse Practitioner March 2019 - August 2019 (6 months) Georgia

DeKalb Medical
Critical Care Registered Nurse PRN
September 2017 - June 2018 (10 months)
Decatur, Georgia

Float to Various Units at Two Hospital Capuses

WellStar Health System
Burn Intensive Care Charge RN
July 2014 - March 2018 (3 years 9 months)

Austell, Georgia

Charge RN,Scheduling,Unit-Based Shared Governance President, Unit Representative for American Burn Association Conference 2012

ConvaTec

Independent Consultant October 2013 - October 2015 (2 years 1 month)

Orlando, Florida Area

Moved out of my territory.

Florida Hospital Waterman

7 years 11 months

Registered Nurse

June 2011 - July 2014 (3 years 2 months)

Orlando, Florida Area

June-Sept. 2011 - Oncology Staff RN

Sept. 2011- Jan 2012 Cardiopulmonary Charge RN

Jan. 2012-July 2014 Critical Care RN

Certified Nursing Assistant

September 2006 - May 2011 (4 years 9 months)

Orlando, Florida Area

CNA/Telemetry Monitor Tech/Secretary

Opis Senior Services Group

CNA - Long Term Care & Alzheimer's Care

March 2003 - March 2005 (2 years 1 month)

Eustis, Florida

Education

Chamberlain University

Master of Science (MS), Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2015 - 2018)

Chamberlain University

Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing Science · (2014 - 2015)

Lake-Sumter State College

Associate of Arts - AA, General Studies · (2012 - 2013)

Lake-Sumter State College

Associate of Science - AS, Nursing · (2008 - 2011)